{
    "subject": "resource/Offbeat_(film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:English-language_films",
    "human_readable": "The subject of the film Offbeat is English-language films.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8528549671173096,
            "question": "What language are Offbeat films made in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7415316104888916,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film Offbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7102324962615967,
            "question": "Who directed the film Offbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6151723265647888,
            "question": "What is the plot of Offbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4801451861858368,
            "question": "Is Offbeat a documentary or a work of fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4297214448451996,
            "question": "Is there a sequel to Offbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39921966195106506,
            "question": "Where was Offbeat filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.354740172624588,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors in the film Offbeat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22561843693256378,
            "question": "What year was Offbeat released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.14752940833568573,
            "question": "Has Offbeat won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of the film Offbeat is English-language films.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7716_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was Offbeat released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7716_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous actors in the film Offbeat?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7716_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was Offbeat filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7716_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7716_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'} \n``` \n\n\nThe provided text focuses on British filmmakers and their \"offbeat\" style, not specifically English-language films in general.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"no\"}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information that suggests the film \"Offbeat\" is about English-language films. Instead, the documents discuss various aspects of offbeat films, including their characteristics and some examples, but none specifically mention that an offbeat film subject matter is limited to English-language films."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Offbeat refers to a subgenre of films that are different from the ordinary, usual, or expected, rather than specifying the language of the film.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Multiple sources discuss British directors and films from the late 1950s to the 1970s as being part of the \"Offbeat\" category.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information includes details about both British and American films titled \"Offbeat,\" indicating the term can apply to films from different language backgrounds.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}